<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://saavangade.github.io/Saavan/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://saavangade.github.io/Saavan/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-11-08T00:25:40-06:00</updated><id>https://saavangade.github.io/Saavan/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Saavan Gade Portfolio</title><subtitle>A senior in AP COMP SCI principles</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Stats</title><link href="https://saavangade.github.io/Saavan/2022/11/07/Stats.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Stats" /><published>2022-11-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2022-11-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://saavangade.github.io/Saavan/2022/11/07/Stats</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[AP STATISTICS AS OF 8/28/2022]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mi</title><link href="https://saavangade.github.io/Saavan/2022/11/07/MI.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mi" /><published>2022-11-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2022-11-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://saavangade.github.io/Saavan/2022/11/07/MI</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[HONORS MEDICAL INTERVENTION AS OF 8/28/2022]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Cbfinal</title><link href="https://saavangade.github.io/Saavan/2022/11/07/CBFINAL.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cbfinal" /><published>2022-11-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2022-11-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://saavangade.github.io/Saavan/2022/11/07/CBFINAL</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[College Board Final Test Questions and Insight Why I got this Question Wrong? I got this question wrong because I thought that it would be more appropriate if we used a numerical value for the number of abcences rather than anything else. The correct response to this would to just use a boolean variable because the abcence can just be reported on true or false. Next time I will make sure to deduce what exactly the problem is asking in terms of the variable function and the continue to match the correct option with what is right.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Government</title><link href="https://saavangade.github.io/Saavan/2022/11/07/Government.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Government" /><published>2022-11-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2022-11-07T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://saavangade.github.io/Saavan/2022/11/07/Government</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[AP GOVERNMENT AS OF 8/28/2022]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Natm</title><link href="https://saavangade.github.io/Saavan/2022/11/06/NATM.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Natm" /><published>2022-11-06T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-11-06T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://saavangade.github.io/Saavan/2022/11/06/NATM</id><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Night at the Museum Blog! During Night at the Museum, the class that I explored was Studio Art. Studio Art displayed a lot of the art pieces that they had been working on throughout the trimester. As I was looking around the classroom there was one piece that caught my eye and it was a picture of a Mily Way bar and a Snickers bar on some cards. My Thoughts and Analysis on the Picture This picture stuck out to me because Night at the Museum was so close to halloween so my eyes just drew to the candy on the wall. I really believe that there is some sort of symbolism behind the drawing as the cards are behing the chocolate. The way I interpret that picture if you are spending money on candy then it should be the two choices resembled here. I really thought whoever drew this drawing did a great job creating this icture and making it appealing. I liked how they creatively put meaning behind the picture as well. I feel like one thing they could imprve on is make the symbolism a little more apparent but I guess the beauty of art is to just let the audience interpret the meaning themselves. Overall I thin NATM was a huge success and us students were able to experience a plethora of talents from a lot of different people. My Rating of the Picture I believe that this picture deserves a 8.5/10. The Picture was very well drawn and I loved how it kind of resembled the Halloween theme that surrounded it. What I Believe They Can Improve On Not much but I feel that if they had to improve on one thing it would be to make the symbolism behind the card in the backround a little more clear. I know that art is based on interpretation of the photograph but if they made it a little more clear then the audience would also be able to better enjoy the piece.]]></summary></entry></feed>